<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelog bulletedList="true">

    <changelogversion changeDate="May 24, 2015" versionName="2.0">
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] Added automatic check for updates and downloading the application.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] The application is restyled in according of the Google Material
            Design concept.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] Added feature to change the language of the application
            interface.
            Available Ukrainian, Russian and English.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] Added feature to select the font (narrow or wide) of the
            application interface.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/ b] Added feature to view the change history of the program.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/ b] Added feature to exit the application by press BACK twice.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>The last used filter conditions are cached and don't re-read from the
            server.
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion changeDate="May 19,2015" versionName="1.2">
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] When the application interacts with the server (queries or
            perform actions) the download dialog appears.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Significantly [b]speed up[/b] downloading of dictionaries cache. Now
            insertion of
            records retrieved from the server to the cache is performed in a single transaction.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[u]Fix[/u] Fixed the background caching of units list when you first start
            the application.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[u]Fix[/u] Fixed sending the attached document (when the URI of the selected
            file is not in the scheme of "file:", but in the scheme of "content").
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="May 12,2015" versionName="1.1">
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] Added the download indicator when list of claims retrieves from
            the server.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] Added the display of the text "No data found according your
            condition." if the conditions do not fit into any one claim.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[b]New![/b] Implemented the caching of the saved queries list (conditions).
            Now the list is read from the server only the first time.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Changed visualization of authorization in the system. Instead of temporary
            pop-up message displays a dialog with a progress bar. Dialog is displayed or until a
            successful login or until an error occurs.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>[u]Fix[/u] Fixed handling the ConnectionTimeOut error. If an error occurs
            at the first attempt to connect to the server after launching the application, then the
            application terminates after closing the error message.
        </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

    <changelogversion changeDate="May 8,2015" versionName="1.0">
        <changelogtext>Initial release.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>


</changelog>